# **Denise Aguirre Martinez**

Buenos Aires, Argentina · linkedin.com/in/denise-aguirre-m/ · +54 9 11 2658 0740 · deniseaguirre.m@gmail.com

Developer Full Stack with a strong focus on Frontend with more than two years of experience in web design focused on usability and accessibility of the interfaces, complementing this last year with skills of Node.js, Nest.js, Express.js, MongoDB and PostgreSQL It is API Integration. I specialize in creating attractive and functional interfaces focused on user experience, with great attention to detail.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Bigger** Remote. Australia Software Developer July 2023-March 2024

- I developed an automated marketing platform for advertising on social networks for brands and influencers, integrating various third-party APIs such as Google Sheets and social networks such as Facebook, TikTok, YouTube and X.
- Implemented component testing on the front-end and controller testing on the back-end.
- I designed and developed the technical documentation and user guide for the project.
- Developed a customer-facing platform for post-construction defect management, offering an all-in-one workflow system that automates and centralizes the scheduling and management of these issues.

## MindHub LA

FullStack Developer Mern

**Buenos Aires, Argentina** 

March 2023-June 2023

- Developed a technology ecommerce web application using MongoDB for database management, Web Services API for data communication and React Native for mobile application development. Node, js powered the backend, ensuring efficient operations on the server.
- I managed the project with Trello, designed with Figma and integrated payments using the MercadoPago API, resulting in a scalable, responsive and feature-rich application that offers optimized user experiences and secure e-commerce functionalities.
- I developed a web-app to upload, read manga and receive donations for developers through MercadoPago, completely in English. Technologies used: ReactJS, NodeJS, MongoDB, Express, Trello, Figma, Redux, MercadoPago API, Tailwind, GitHub.

#### National University of José C. Paz

Technical assistant of the Virtual UNPAZ Management Department

**Buenos Aires, Argentina** 

August 2019-March 2023

- Moodle database administration and virtual classroom design with HTML and CSS
- User management and virtual classrooms.
- Preparation of frequently asked questions and tutorials.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF JOSÉ C. PAZ

University Technician in Electronic Commerce

Use: 8.86

**Buenos Aires, Argentina** 

August 2017-December 2020

### **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

- Language: Native Spanish
- Web design and digital communication
- Beginning programming with Python
- Testing QA Manual
- Wireframe Creation
- Problem resolution
- Agile Methodology
- Accessibility and usability
- Attention to detail
- Autodidact

## **TECHNICAL ABILITIES**

Frontend: React.js, Next.js, JavaScript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Redux, Axios, Material UI.

Backend: Node.js, Nest.js, Express.js, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Docker.

**Test:** Cypress, Jest, Postman.

Tools: GitHub, Trello, Figma, ClickUp, Google Drive.

Portfolio: <a href="https://denise-aguirre-m.netlify.app/">https://denise-aguirre-m.netlify.app/</a>
GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/DeniseAguirre">https://github.com/DeniseAguirre</a>